Julie Davis

Dedicated Office Manager with Extensive Software Knowledge

Huntington, IN juliedavis6577_2zr@indeedemail.com 2602243848

Dependable and organized office management professional with 20+ years experience handling a wide range of administrative, technical and executive support tasks.

Willing to relocate to: Middleburg, FL - Indianapolis, IN Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Office Manager

Foil Die International - Huntington, IN March 2003 to Present

Employee Time Entry Payroll Functions Weekly Tax Functions Monthly State Tax Functions Quarterly FED Tax Functions Payable Receivables/Invoicing Direct Telephone Calls Purchasing for office/janitorial/perishable shop supplies Facilitate Human Resource Functions: - Advertise for open positions - Process Resumes for open positions, arrange interviews - Health Insurance applications, questions, and selection of provider - Simple IRA applications, deposits & reporting - Vacation tracking - Policy management & updates Process Customer requests-telephone, fax, email, web Process Direct Visitors Facilitating Company Functions Updating Open Job List Weekly Updating Open Job List at month end Shipping/schedule shipments/prepare BOL & packing lists Technical Skills: 1. Spreadsheets (Excel/Google Sheets) 2. Asana (Project Management) 3. E2 (Job Shop Scheduling) 4. QuickBooks (Accounting Entry)

Office Manager

Trinity Tool - Huntington, IN 1998 to 2003

Employee Time Entry Payroll Facilitated tax payments Accounts Receivables/Invoicing Accounts Payables

Greeted guests and answered/directed phone calls

Education

Cosmetology in Cosmetology

Huntington Beauty School - Huntington, IN 1975 to 1976

High school diploma in General

Huntington North High School - Huntington, IN September 1971 to May 1975

Skills

- Payroll
- Administrative Experience
- Accounts Payable
- Office Management
- Accounts Payable
- Administrative Experience
- Office Management
- QuickBooks
- Payroll
- Event Planning
- Accounts Receivable
- Accounting
- Human Resources
- Microsoft Outlook
- Data Entry
- Account Reconciliation
- Microsoft Excel